postwaves.com 2018-12-27

# PRIVACY POLICY - Postwaves

Your privacy is important to us. Postwaves is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to the Postwaves.com website and its subdomains (refered to as Postwaves or Postwaves.com) governs data collection and usage. This Privacy Policy, together with our Terms and Conditions, provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By creating an account with Postwaves or using the Postwaves.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this policy.

**COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Postwaves.com website collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, user name, address or telephone number when you sign up for our website and access it. Postwaves.com also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code and country.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Postwaves.com. This information (log data) can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Postwaves.com to deliver personalized service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding the use of the Postwaves.com website. Except for the IP address you use to create the account, all IP addresses will be deleted from our servers after 90 days.

When you sign up with twitter, your Username will be your twitter name. All Users of Postwaves will be able to recognize your Username as your twitter name and may contact you on twitter. You agree that Postwaves or any of its Users contacting you on twitter regarding your activities on Postwaves. We shall not be responsible or liable for any activities on twitter by you or other Users.

The posts and comments you make on Postwaves are not private, even if made to a Postwaves group not readily accessible to the public. Your messages are generally only viewable by the parties involved. Postwaves.com does not read any of your private online communications unless requested by you to provide support and will not be responsible for its content and use by third parties. However, we keep a complete log of all messages sent on our service, even when both parties later terminate their accounts.

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Postwaves.com does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Website from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Website at any time or in any manner. If Postwaves.com learns that personally identifiable information of persons below 13 years of age has been collected on the Website without verified parental consent, then Postwaves.com will take appropriate steps to delete this information.

**USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Postwaves.com collects and uses your personal information to operate the Postwaves.com website and also to improve your experience. We use the personal information to know your preferences and your interactions with the site to allow you to customize your experience, subscriptions, preferred language, accumulated reputation, voting data, and date of last login. We also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Postwaves.com and its affiliates. We may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Postwaves.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. We may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. When you subscribe to our mailing list, Postwaves.com may use it for email marketing, but protect the users’ information and make sure it is secure. All third parties whose services are used by Postwaves are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Postwaves.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Postwaves.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Postwaves.com keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Postwaves.com, in order to determine what Postwaves.com services are the most popular. This data may be used to deliver customized content and advertising within Postwaves.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

**GOOGLE  ANALYTICS**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of postwaves.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find [Google’s privacy policy here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

**DISCLOSING YOUR INFORMATION**

Postwaves.com website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Postwaves.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Postwaves.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Postwaves.com, or the public.

We reserve the right to delay notice to users in cases involving the exploitation of minors and when we believe a delay is necessary to prevent imminent and serious bodily harm to a person.

**CALIFORNIA’S ‘DO NOT TRACK’ LAW**

Postwaves’s website does not currently respond to a Do Not Track (“DNT”) or similar signal as it awaits the results of efforts by the policy and legal community to determine the meaning of DNT and the proper way to respond.

**USE OF COOKIES**

Postwaves.com website may gather information about your general internet use by using cookies.  Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Postwaves.com website uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience.

Postwaves.com website may also gather information such as IP address, internal session ID, user’s domain, type of Internet browser, domain of Website. Such information will not identify you personally: it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save your time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Postwaves.com pages, or register with Postwaves.com site or services, a cookie helps Postwaves.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information. When you return to the same Postwaves.com website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Postwaves.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Postwaves.com services or websites you visit.

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Postwaves.com is in beta testing stage meaning a lot will change in the near future. During the changes for development and improvement of the site, there may be some impact on the personal information that you provide. Hence, provide only the information that is necessary for using the site and keep track of your personal information until the site completes beta testing stage and becomes fully operational.

Postwaves.com may transfer your personal information and submitted content that Postwaves.com collects from you to our main server located in the United States of America for processing and storing. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Postwaves.com will take all reasonable steps to make sure that your data is treated securely without any loss, misuse or alteration of information and in agreement with this Privacy Policy.  Postwaves.com secures the information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Postwaves does not allow other parties to collect personally identifiable information from users on Postwaves.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your data.

Postwaves make every effort to secure any personal information submitted to us by users. We provide access to user data to only such employees who are assigned to render the required services. The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore Postwaves.com cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk.

**ACCOUNT TERMINATION**

You can terminate your account at any time. On termination of your account, your user name associated with the terminated account will not be available for others to use, and your public profile is no longer visible to Postwaves users. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or termination of your account. However, we will not sell, transfer, or use the information relating to the terminated account of an individual in any way.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY AND OPT-OUT**

Postwaves.com will occasionally change/update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback and to meet the changing needs of Postwaves. We may notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our web pages. However, Postwaves.com encourages you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how Postwaves.com is protecting your information.

YOU MAY CHOOSE TO “OPT-OUT”/STOP RECEIVING OUR NEWSLETTER OR MARKETING EMAILS BY FOLLOWING THE UNSUBSCRIBE LINK INCLUDED IN THESE EMAILS OR BY SENDING AN E-MAIL TO [privacy@postwaves.com](mailto:privacy@postwaves.com).

**INFRINGEMENT**

If you observe that someone has infringed your rights, or believe that someone has submitted, without your permission, to Postwaves a link to a photograph, video, or digital image of you which you consider is vulgar or is objectionable, please contact us at [privacy@postwaves.com](mailto:privacy@postwaves.com), and we will expedite its removal as quickly as possible. Postwaves respects your privacy and prohibits the posting of such content without consent.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

Postwaves.com welcomes your suggestions and questions regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that Postwaves.com has not adhered to this Policy, please contact Postwaves.com at [privacy@postwaves.com](mailto:privacy@postwaves.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
